eznettools.com 2013-05-20

# EZ-NetTools - Bid Proposal Online Presenter

EZ-NetTools, Inc. respects the privacy of its customers and the visitors and users of its websites.

This Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") is intended to inform you of our policies and practices regarding the collection, use and disclosure of any personal information we obtain about you based upon your use of our website, products or services. "Personal Information" is information about you that is personally identifiable to you such as your name, address, e-mail address, phone number, any transactions you conduct on our websites or offline with us, as well as other non-public information that is associated with the foregoing.

We pay close attention to how Personal Information is used and shared, and we use Personal Information sensibly.

We act as a service provider to our customers and may process and store on behalf of our customers Personal Information that our customers collect about third parties. We do not own that Personal Information.

## User Consent

By visiting our website or using our products or services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

You expressly consent to the processing of your Personal Information according to this Privacy Policy. 

## Collection of Personal Information

The Personal Information we gather from you helps us learn about our customers and potential customers. We use this information to better tailor the features, performance and support of our solutions, products and services, and to contact you from time to time with information and offers about our products and services.

## Personal Information You Provide to Us

We collect Personal Information that you submit to us voluntarily. The Personal Information we collect includes, but is not limited to, the following: name, mailing address, Web address, telephone number, e-mail address, and information contained in any e-mail or other communication you send to us or information you give to us in any other way. 

## Personal Information Collected via Technology

As you navigate our website, certain passive information may also be collected, including your Internet Protocol address, browser type, and operating system. We also use cookies, a small file stored by your web browser on your computer, and navigational data like Uniform Resource Locators (URLs) to gather information regarding the date and time of your visit and the solutions and information for which you searched and viewed. This type of information is collected to make our solutions and services more useful to you by understanding what pages you click on during your visit to our websites. Such information will allow us to improve and personalize your experience 

Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. You can set your browser to disable cookies. However, if you choose not to accept cookies, we may not be able to provide you with as good of an experience as one that is specifically tailored to your needs by utilizing the cookie. 

## Personal Information We Receive from Other Sources

We may receive Personal Information about you from other sources like telephone or fax. We may add this information to the information we have already collected about you in order to improve the solutions and services we provide.

## Use of Information

In general, Personal Information you submit to us is used either to set up solutions or purchase website marketing services, respond to requests that you make, to process transactions, to facilitate your request for a quote from a third party service provider or to aid us in serving you better. We do not share your Personal Information with other businesses. We may use your Personal Information to provide you with electronic newsletters or promotional e-mails as well as information and offers about our products and services.

## Disclosure of Personal Information

Except as otherwise stated in this Privacy Policy, we do not sell your Personal Information to third parties. In order to build the solutions for you, we may engage third parties to assist us, and, in connection with such assistance, we may provide them with Personal Information that you have provided and that is necessary for them to assist us. 

To drive traffic to your website and to make your website easier to find, we will disclose keywords about your business, your business name, general and specific description about your business, information about your location, and information about your products and services to third-party services (such as search engines) and to the general public.

We may also use third parties to maintain and store your Personal Information and to process any payment you make to us. Generally, these third parties are required not to use your Personal Information other than to provide the services requested by EZ-NetTools Inc..

If our company or our assets are acquired by another company, that company will possess the Personal Information collected by us and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

We may disclose your Personal Information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to (a) comply with relevant laws or to respond to subpoenas or warrants served on EZ-NetTools Inc.; or (b) to protect and defend the rights or property of EZ-NetTools or users of our websites or our customers' websites.

## Your Choices Regarding Your Personal Information

Should you decide to stop receiving e-mail communications or newsletters from us, you will have the opportunity to "opt-out" by following the unsubscribe instructions provided in the e-mail. If at any time you wish to subscribe to any communications from us, you may do so by contacting us at sales@eznettools.com. Despite your indicated e-mail preferences, we may send you e-mail regarding updates to legal notices applicable to the account you created with us. From time to time, we may contact you by telephone to offer you products or services which we believe may be valuable to you. Should you prefer not to receive such calls, please advise the representative who contacts you or contact customer care.

## Regarding Minors

Our websites are not designed for minors under the age of 18. We do not intentionally gather Personal Information about visitors who are under the age of 18.

## Links to Other Sites

Our provision of a link to any other website or location is for your convenience and does not signify our endorsement of such other website or location or its contents. We have no control over, do not review, and cannot be responsible for these outside websites or their content. Please be aware that the terms of our Privacy Policy do not apply to these outside websites.

## Security

We use reasonable measures to maintain the security of your Personal Information. Even so, technical mistakes are possible. No company, including EZ-NetTools Inc., can fully eliminate security risks associated with Personal Information.

## Contact Us

Should you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Statement, please contact us:

EZ-NetTools, Inc.  
238 East 3000 North

Rexburg, ID 83440  
Phone: (208) 356-8361

## Privacy Statement Updates

This Privacy Policy is subject to occasional revision, and if we make any changes in the way we use your Personal Information, we shall notify you by posting an updated Private Policy at www.eznettools.com. If you object to any such changes, you must cease using our website, products or services. Continued use of our website, products or services following notice of any such changes shall indicate your acknowledgment of such changes and agreement to be bound by the terms and conditions of such changes. 

## Choice of Law

If you choose to visit EZ-NetTools's website or use our products or services, any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy as governed by the laws of the State of Idaho.
